hamariweb.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy - Hamariweb.com

ہماری ویب , ہر لحاظ سے اپنے ویب سائٹ وزیٹرز اور سبسکرائبرز کی پرائیوسی کا خیال رکھتی ہے- اطمینان رکھئیے کہ آپ کی مہیا کردہ معلومات سو فیصد محفوظ ہیں- ہماری مکمل پرائیوسی پالیسی درج ذیل ہے

* * *

**Hamariweb** believes that trust is an important component of the service we provide to our visitors and subscribers. To ensure that we earn and keep that trust, Hamariweb makes every effort to protect your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information. This Privacy Policy is provided to inform you about Hamariweb's collection, use and disclosure of information you choose to share with us through the Site. 

This Privacy Policy is considered to be a part of Hamariweb's User Agreement. By using the Sites you agree to the terms and conditions of the User Agreement, including this Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you are also consenting to Hamariweb's privacy practices, including the use and disclosure of any personally identifiable information that you have shared with us, as described in this Privacy Policy. 

We never rent, sell or share any information you give us. You privacy is important to us! When you visit the Hamariweb.com site, we collect some basic information that does not identify individual users. This includes which pages are visited, types of form submitted, and any feedback from our visitors. We then collate this information with other pieces of information to improve our site and make your experience on the site as valuable and efficient as possible. Information are provided to authorized institutions only in case of legal requirement by the law of land.   

**Advertisment on Hamariweb.com:**

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [ Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [ http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

You acknowledge that Hamariweb.com does not control the performance of advertisers that appear on Hamariweb.com. Therefore, if you choose to purchase a product or service, you release us from any and all claims you may have regarding the third party's failure to deliver or perform. We use other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website.

**Information Collection and Use:**

For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to Location, Phone Number, Device Storage. The information that we request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy. 

The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you. 

Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app 

Google Play Services  
AdMob  
Firebase Analytics  
Fabric  
Crashlytics

Security 

we value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
